<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyKotlinApp</string>
    <string name="BasketDes">
         * Rectangular 15 L bucket with squeezer Stable and durable bucket with a capacity of up to 15 liters to the needs of the most demanding customers.
        \n\n* Included with the so-called a self-clamping juicer that allows you to squeeze the MOP tip faster and more effectively. Closes under pressure like a cup , causing pressure on the tip on each side.
        \n\n* The squeezer has a special handle to hold the stick with MOP. Inside the bucket there is a measuring cup for measuring the necessary amount of liquids.
        \n\n* There is a so-called "spout" helps in getting rid of the contents of the bucket.
        \n\n* The comfortable handle makes it easy to move the bucket , and the special recess under the fingers makes it easy to hold the bucket when pouring liquids</string>
    <string name="SmartBuckeMopDes">
            Colour   :   Multicolour
        \n\nHandle Material   :   Stainless,Steel Handle,Stainless-steel
        \n\nIncluded Components   :    MOP
        \n\nItem Volume   :    5 Litres
        \n\nSpecial Feature    :    Spin Mop Bucket
        \n\nNet Quantity    :    1.00 count</string>
    <string name="BUCKET_MOP_Des">
\n\nColour : Blue
\nMaterial : Plastic
\nHandle Material : Plastic
\nHead Material : Microfiber
\nSpecial Feature	Spin Mop Bucket
    </string>
    <string name="PUSH_CHOPPER_Des">
        \nBrand : Snazzynest
\nMaterial : Stainless Steel, Plastic
\nColour : Multicolor
\nProduct Dimensions : 	10L x 10W x 20H Centimeters
\nProduct Care : Hand Wash
    </string>
    <string name="ThreeDABBASET_Des">

\nBrand : 	MERIL
\nColour  :  Multicolor
\nMaterial : 	Plastic
\nNumber of Sets :	3
\nIs Dishwasher Safe : Yes
    </string>
    <string name="SMALLDABBASET_Des">Dabba Set, 3 Piece,Pink - 5 L, 7 L, 10 L Plastic Grocery Container
Material : Plastic
Net Quantity  : Pack of 3
Country of Origin : India</string>
    <string name="BIGDABBASET_Des"> Features

    - Type: Spice Set

    . Color: Blue

    . Material: Plastic

    Capacity: 250 ml

    In The Box

    Sales Package

    3 pcs

    Pack of

    3

    General

    Brand

    Shopinclass

    Model Name

    Dabba Set Plastic Box Grocery Containers With Spoon Set of 3 Pcs Blue Color

    Model Number

    HD14

    Type

    Spice Set

    Material

    Plastic

    Color

    Blue

    Shade

    Blue

    Capacity

    250 ml

    Shape

    Cylindrical

    Dimensions

    Width

    2.83 inch

    Height

    2.7 inch

    Weight

    140 g

    Other Dimensions

    Length-7.2 cms Width- 7 cms
    </string>
    <string name="INSULATEDWATERBOTTLE_Des">Made from 18/8 food-grade stainless steel
Designed with triple insulated vacuum-sealed double walls to keep your drinks safe
The double walled water bottle with a new leak-proof &amp; sweat-proof design
Available in eight stylish colours and patterns
Safe and healthy to use, low maintenance steel bottles
Comes with a sports cap and a straw cap for utility</string>
    <string name="MASALDABBA_Des">BrandPrimelife
ColourBrown
MaterialPlastic
Material FeatureBPA Free
Capacity1500 Milliliters
Number of Sets7
Special FeatureAir Tight
Closure TypeCork
Is Dishwasher SafeYes
Material Type FreeBPA Free</string>
    <string name="ROYALMASALARACKSET_Des">* Package content: Spice rack with 16/24 jars. \n\n* Jars are made by high quality BPA free food grade PP plastic material and spice rack is made by high quality ABS thermoplastic which makes this spice rack unbreakable.\n\n*
360 Degree Rotation- This spice rack has 360-degree revolving feature which helps to find the desire spice more quickly. \n\n* And this beautiful spice rack will add beauty to your kitchen area.\n\n* It has compact design that takes only small place in your kitchen cabinet.\n\n*
Detachable Parts- All parts of this spice rack are easily detachable which helps for easy cleaning. \n\n* And spice jar pickup from spice rack also very easy. \n\n* All jars are arranged in a symmetrical manner which makes this spice rack more elegant.</string>
    <string name="MASALARACK_Des">* Capacity: Each Jar 200 ml And Useful For Tableware, 100% food grade and dishwasher safe
Masalas, Spice storage, Dining table Easy to Move And Small Size so Best for Kitchen Dining Table.\n\n*  The spice Canisters are easy to use, allowing for one handed operation and each spice canister.\n\n* 
Dispense all kinds of spices, seasonings, powders, and other ingredients and have a uniformly classic set of ingredients in your pantry or kitchen. \n\n*  with its clear, you no longer have to search through numerous packages while cooking just to find the perfect spice that you need just a quick and easy access to your condiments.\n\n* 
Transparent Jars with Rotatable Lids- The jars of this spice rack are made by food grade material. \n\n*  It has transparent body which helps in easy accessibility of spices. \n\n*  Jars have rotatable lids with 2-hole section for easy dispense.</string>
    <string name="MILTONBATHROOMSET_Des">MaterialPlastic
ColourBlack And Silver
BrandLiza
Included ComponentsStool, Bucket, Mug
Number of Pieces3
Finish TypeGlossy, Painted

\n\n* Additional Information
Manufacturer: Liza
Packer: Liza
Item Weight: 1 kg 920 g
Net Quantity: 3.00 count
Included Components: Stool, Bucket, Mug</string>
    <string name="MILTONDUMBELLS_Des">BrandMilton
Colour:Green
Technical Specifications:Bucket: L x W x H - 15 x 13.5 x 13 Inches; Deep Bucket: L x W x H - 6.5 x 16 x 9 Inches; Mug: L x W x H - 7 x 5 x 4.7 Inches; Crown Patla: L x W x H - 11.5 x 11.5 x 8 Inches; Dustbin: L x W x H - 10.5 x 10 x 10 Inches Soap Dish: L x W x H - 7 x 4.5 x 1.3 Inches
Pack Content:6 Piece Set
Weight:3.6 Kg
Material:Plastic
SKUHC1698084-S-PM25549
</string>
    <string name="MILTONDUPLEX_Des">BrandMilton
Colour:Green
Technical Specifications:Bucket: L x W x H - 15 x 13.5 x 13 Inches; Deep Bucket: L x W x H - 6.5 x 16 x 9 Inches; Mug: L x W x H - 7 x 5 x 4.7 Inches; Crown Patla: L x W x H - 11.5 x 11.5 x 8 Inches; Dustbin: L x W x H - 10.5 x 10 x 10 Inches Soap Dish: L x W x H - 7 x 4.5 x 1.3 Inches
Pack Content:6 Piece Set
Weight:3.6 Kg
Material:Plastic
SKUHC1698084-S-PM25549</string>
    <string name="MILTONWATERBOTTLE_Des">
        \nBrand : 	MILTON
\nCapacity : 1.05 litres
\nColour	Black
\nSpecial Feature :\n\t	Double Wall Vacuum Insulated, Durable, Rust proof, Leakproof
\nModel Name : Aura 1000,Black</string>
    <string name="TSSIUEPAPER_Des">
        \nColour : Multicolour
\nSize : 100 Count (Pack of 3)
\nMaterial :	Paper
\nBrand :	Softouch Ply Rating	1-Ply</string>
    <string name="TOILETPAPER_Des">
\nBrand	: Amazon Brand - Solimo
\nSpecial Feature : Absorbent
\nNet Quantity	: 4 count
\nMaterial	: Paper
\nSheet Count : 300
\nPly Rating : 3-Ply
\nRecommended Uses For Product	Bathroom
\nMaterial Feature	: Chemical Free
\nScent	: Unscented
\nSize	300 Count (Pack of 4)
</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>